<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>g-c.dev</title>
    <link>https://g-c.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on g-c.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:10:47 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://g-c.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aqualung Without Jethro</title>
      <link>https://g-c.dev/posts/aqualung-without-jethro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:10:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-c.dev/posts/aqualung-without-jethro/</guid>
      <description>Aqualung -Jethro Yep, that&amp;rsquo;s the search key to use if you want to look up on Google information for this incredible artist.
I want to start this new category, &amp;ldquo;lets-take-a-break&amp;rdquo;, where sometime I will share some of my favourite ways of taking a break.
Most of the time is listening to some my favourite music artists. And today, I&amp;rsquo;ll start with Aqualung.
He&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly elegant and talented british artist. In his music, you can listen influences from the best inspirations out there: Beatles, Tears for Fears, Radiohead, Bon Iver, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform and Layered Infrastructure (part I)</title>
      <link>https://g-c.dev/posts/terraform-and-layered-infrastructure-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 17:52:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-c.dev/posts/terraform-and-layered-infrastructure-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Current state of the art We all know, Terraform is the current de-facto standard when it comes to describe your infrastructure.
We might also have experienced some limitation in flexibility when we used Terraform (mostly the versions &amp;lt; 1.0) for which we had to implement quite often some hackish workaround: thinking about conditional logic, &amp;ldquo;for-each&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; when there was no foreach support, etc&amp;hellip;
Luckily most of these can masked via modules, a quite flexible representation of logical group of resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oAuth2Proxy, Azure AD and Traefik</title>
      <link>https://g-c.dev/posts/oauth2proxy-and-traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 18:58:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-c.dev/posts/oauth2proxy-and-traefik/</guid>
      <description>Summary oAuth2Proxy is a nice component for Kubernetes that adds an authentication layer, transparently, on top of your workload.
The deployment of oAuth2Proxy is quite straightforward, via Helm, but when it comes to the integration with the authentication providers, some complexity arises, mainly due to the fact the documentation is not very complete. To be fair, oAuth2Proxy supports a lot of backends, and while some of these are well documented, for some others the documentation is very limited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
